# **CHARLIE MASON**

# **Undergraduate Gameplay Programmer**

**\** 07747867911

@ charlie.mason020@gmail.com

<sub>ළ</sub> charliemason.net

# **SUMMARY**

I'm an undergraduate with key skills in Unreal Engine and C++ soon to graduate in 2023. I'm particularly interested in games design especially focused on gameplay engineering, I enjoy learning how to create new game mechanics and systems that add to the player's experience.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Web Designer, Web Developer

iii 01/2023 - Present ♀ Remote

Building a website portfolio to present myself and projects

- Created the different pages using HTML
- Developed the pages with CSS to improve the visual aspects
- Small Javascript implentation for loading screen between pages

#### Gameplay Tester & Recorder Freelancing

Axia Labs, Upwork

**iii** 11/2022 - 02/2023

Remote

Online media videography company

Recorded high quality gameplay from battle simulator games consisting of (Ultimate Epic Battle Simulator 2, TABS, Overgrown, Insurgency: Sandstorm)

# Live Streamer, Content Creator

#### **Twitch**

**=** 06/2020 - 02/2023

Remote

Created professional live streams each week to an audience online. Edited and published videos to follow these live streams

- Presented live streams multiple times a week, consisting of gameplay with commentary
- Built a community through social media with posts in different gaming communities and community servers
- Organised channel events with rewards through the community
- Weekly video uploads with edited gameplay and commentary

# **EDUCATION**

#### **BSc Games Development**

**Norwich University of the Arts** 

UAL Level 3 Extended Diploma in Games Design & Animation

# **Chelmsford College**

**=** 09/2018 - 06/2020

↑ Chelmsford, United Kingdom

# UAL Level 2 Diploma in creative media production and technology

# **Chelmsford College**

# **SKILLS**

**Python Blender HTML Microsoft Office Suite** Unity C++ C# **Unreal Engine 4/5** Git Java **CSS Photoshop Premiere Pro After Effects** 

# **STRENGTHS**

#### **Flexibility**

Commited to new projects or helping others work to complete tasks efficiently. Whether it's remote or in an office environment.



#### **Results Driven**

Devoted to the key goals, delivering workloads with excellent quality and within time contrains.



#### **Enthusiastic Leamer**

Enthusiastic to learn new coding languages or methods of improving performance, always seeking to improve myself.

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**



#### **Released Game**

Produced and published my own game over the last 4 months of my university course, frequently updating it with new content, the game has received praise by players.



#### My Personal Website!

Developed and created my first website using HTML and CSS, frequently updating.



#### **Professional Pitch**

Participated with other students to develop a basic game and pitch presentation for a games studio within a short deadline. This was well received by the company, they advised we would get funding for this.